Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities records, 1960-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 4: New Civics, 1974-2012; (27 boxes)
  - Subseries 4.3: Regional Strategies, 1974-2012; (5 boxes)
    - The Regionalist: Practical Models of Regional Governance (Fall 1998), 1997 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Report to the Convention and Vistors Bureau of Elkhart, Indiana, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Scranton/Wilkes Barre Report, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Smart Growth Fit for a King, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Somerset Shared Services Neighborhood Group Special Reports, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - State of the Region Forum, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - State of the Region Forum, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Steps Toward Regional Solutions: the Rochester Forum, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Temporary Paradise? A Look at the Special Landscape of the San Diego Region, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Towards a National Regional Agenda: Building Regional Communities for the 21st Century, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4.4: Visioning and Local Participation, 1974-2012; (8 boxes)
    - Action Plan: Urban Forum Workshop November 4, 1991; San Diego, California (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Action Plan: Urban Forum Workshop November 4, 1991; San Diego, California (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Action Plan: Urban Forum Workshop November 4, 1991; San Diego, California (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Action Plan: Urban Forum Workshop November 4, 1991; San Diego, California (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - American Communities Partnership Report: Planning for Building a Shared Future, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Brea Redevelopment Agency: Twenty-two Acre Retail Request for Proposals, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Brea by Design: The Downtown Charrette, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Calgary Downtown Business Revitalization Zone Calgary 20/20: Calgarians Choosing their Future Today, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Calgary Downtown Business Revitalization Zone Vision 20/20 Report, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - City Center Vision and Strategic Plan: Report by the City of Tucson, Arizona, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - City Leaders Institute on Aging in Place, March 22 2012 Meeting Materials (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - City of Myrtle Beach Vision Program, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Colorado Boulevard: Our Main Street Vision for the 21st Century Pasadena, California, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Colorado Springs: a Shared Vision, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Colorado Springs: a Shared Vision, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Columbia Voyage: Discovering Columbia, MD: Tomorrow's the Launch, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Community Assessment Forum and Recommendations for Small Communities to Address Their Issues for Social Revitalization, A Report on Woodlake Vicinity, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Dublin Community Plan: Visioning Report, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Dublin Community Plan: Visioning Report, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Dublin Community Plan: Visioning Report, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Dublin Community Plan: Visioning Report, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Dublin Community Plan: Visioning Report, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Final Report of Comprehensive Planning and Public Participation Program, Oxford, Ohio, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Goals for a Greater Rochester, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Greater Knoxville Beautification Board -Knoxville, Knox County 2000, A Vision for the Future, October 18-19, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - In Pursuit of Livability: A Strategic Planning Cooperative -- Public Participation, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - It's Time: A Vision for the Greater Myrtle Beach Community Vision Ideas, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - It's Time: A Vision for the Greater Myrtle Beach Community Vision Ideas, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Leeds United Report of Research for the Vision of Leeds prepared by URBED, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Livable Delaware, 2010 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - National Capital Region Transportation Planning Board: Shaping Transportation Solutions, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Neighbors Building Neighborhoods: Progress Report, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Oxford Tomorrow: A Vision for the Future, Comprehensive Plan for Oxford, Ohio, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Oxford Tomorrow: A Vision for the Future, Comprehensive Plan for Oxford, Ohio, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Report on the Shared Vision Conference: Building a Great Community, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Report on Visit to Fayetteville, Arkansas, May 24-25, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Report on Weehawken Design Charrette, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Report to Metro Visions: Kick Off Forum Summary of Responses Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Report to the City of Fontana: Responses from the Focus Group Meetings, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Responses for the Grand Travers County Meeting, May 1990 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Revision 2000, Community with a Vision: A Map for our Future (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - San Diego Retreat for Partners for Livable San Diego, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - San Diego Retreat for Partners for Livable San Diego, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - San Diego: Looking to the Future, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Shaping Growth in American Communities Site Visit Report, Rochester, NY, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Shared Vision Report to the Community, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Summary of the Neighbors Building Neighborhood Process from Planning to Implementation, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Trends in Arlington Workshop- 11/30/1993 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Trends in Arlington Workshop- 11/30/1993 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Vice-Chancellors Summit, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Vision 20/20: A Facilities Plan for Four Arlington County Departments, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Vision for the Anacostia Watershed Leadership Forum Transcript, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Vision for the Anacostia Watershed Leadership Forum: Final Report to the US Environmental Protection Agency, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Vision for the Anacostia Watershed Leadership Forum: Final Report to the US Environmental Protection Agency, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Vision for the Anacostia Watershed Leadership Forum: Final Report to the US Environmental Protection Agency, `993 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Vision Plan (50-year) for the Downtown Area of Sarasota, Florida: Interim Report Summary, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Vision Process Report/Community Plan, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Visioning: Public Partnership and Stewardship Position Paper, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Visions and Goals: The Essentials of Leadership, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Voices & Visions: Summary Report Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Voices & Visions: Summary Report Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Voices & Visions: Summary Report Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Working Paper on Fontana Design Charrette, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Series 5: Partners' Resources, 1967-2012; (21 boxes)
  Series 5, Partners Resources, includes the materials necessary for the workings and advertising of Partners of Livable Communities and its affiliates throughout the United States.
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 2006 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 2007 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 2009 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Amenities - National Council of Amenity Planners, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Amenities Newsletter of the National Council of Amenity Planners, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - America's Most Livable Communities and Entrepreneurial American Leadership Program, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - America's Most Livable Communities Awards Program, April 20, 2004 at the National Press Club (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - America's Most Livable Website Brochure, 2000 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - America's Oldest Buildings Engagement Calendar for 1988 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Bay Area Partners: Three-Year Plan, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Partnership Announcement Poster, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Partnership brochure, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Binder, March 1st 2002 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees Binder, March 1st 2002 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Binder, March 1st 2002 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Resource Binder, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Briefing Book on Partners for Livable Places, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Building Leadership, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Building Leadership/Creating Solutions, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - By Design 2, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Celebrating 30 Years of Awards, 2011 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Celebration of Community Spirit Awards Program, 2002 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - City Wide Amenity Resource Invetory, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Community Assistance, Special Issue of Livability, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Community Futures Newsletter, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Community Futures Newsletter, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Community Potentials Magazine, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Community Potentials Magazine, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Community Potentials Magazine, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Design Arts/Visual Arts Collaboration Meeting, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Design Arts 1: Grants Recognition Program, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Directory of Resources: 1975-2011 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Economics of Amenity Brochure, Richmond, VA, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Economics of Amenity Publication Poster, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Economics of Amenity Set (October 1980-August 1981) (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Focus: A Design Arts Film and Video Guide, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Founders Award for Civic Leadership A Celebration of Improving Livability Through Design, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Founders Award for Civic Leadership to Henry G. Cisneros and William H. Hudnut, III, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Founders Award for Civic Leadership to Nancy Hanks, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Founders Award for Civic Leadership to Senator Richard Lugar, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Gala Celebration of American Cities, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Gala Celebration of American Communities Program, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Grant Recognition Program for Design, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Guide to Partners' Livability Clearinghouse, A, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Honors Program at Union Station Gala, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Information Packets, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Information Packets, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Information Packets, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Information Packets, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Information Packets, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Insights On Sights: Perspectives on Art in Public Places -- Brochure, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Interview with Robert H. McNulty, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Learning from America: What Makes Cities Livable Handbook on Urban Improvement, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Livability by Design Awards Programs, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Livability Central, 2011 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Livability Central: A Research and Technical Assistance Center Dedicated to Community Livability, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Livability Clearinghouse -- 1987 - 1992 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Livability Consulting for Smaller Communities, 2010 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Livability Digest, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Livability Directory - December 2008 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Livability Directory - December 2008 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Livability Directory 1, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Livability Directory 2, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Livability Directory 3, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Livability Resources, by the Livability Clearinghouse, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Livability Set, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Livability Set, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Livability: An Issue of Environmental Comments, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Long Range Strategic Planning Binder Special Committee to the Board, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Long Range Strategic Planning Binder Special Committee to the Board, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Long-Serving Trustees, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Marketing the "America's Most Livable Cities" Website, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Mayors Leadership Forum for Livable Communities Newsletter, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - New and Renewable American Community: Local Solutions to National Problems, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - New Consulting Service for Municipalities, Corporations and Foundations, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - On the 35th Anniversary: A Renewed Vision of Livability, Serving the American Community, 2011 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Partners Activities Report, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Partners Activities Report, 1988, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Partners Activities Report, 1988, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Partners Biannual Report, 1983 - 1985 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Partners Biannual Report, 1986 - 1988 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Partners Corporate Sponsorship Program for Partners for Livable Places, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Partners Council National Recognition Program 1984 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Partners for a Livable Minnesota, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Partners for Livable Australia Brochure, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Partners for Livable Asia, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Partners for Livable Communities - Twentieth Anniversary Program, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Partners for Livable Communities 1999 Brochure (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Partners for Livable Communities 2002 Brochure (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Partners for Livable Communities Employee's Manual, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Partners for Livable Communities Global Agenda, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Partners for Livable Communities Publications Catalog, 1999 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Partners for Livable Communities: Meeting the Challenges of the Emerging American Community Business Plan, 1993 1996, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Partners for Livable Indiana: Plan of Action, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Partners for Livable Places 1978 Brochure (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Partners for Livable Places 1978 Brochure (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Partners for Livable Places 1983 Brochure (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Partners for Livable Places 1989 Brochure, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Partners for Livable Places 2nd Annual Meeting, Livability in Times of Constraint, 1979 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Partners for Livable Places Christmas Card, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Partners for Livable Places First Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Partners for Livable Places In house newsletter, Nov 3, 1978-May 9, 1979 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Partners for Livable Places San Diego Brochure, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Partners for Livable Places: Helping Communities Build a Brighter Future, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Partners for Livable Places: Helping Communities Build a Brighter Future Brochure, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Partners for Livable Places' Community Assistance Program, Livability, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Partners Honors: Awards and Celebrations, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Partners in Washington - First Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Partners Indiana Brochure, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study Final Report, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Partners Indiana: Strategies for the New Decade I, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Partners Indiana: Strategies for the New Decade II, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Partners Indiana: in Affiliation with Partners for Livable Places, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Partners News, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Partners News, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Partners News, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Partners West Community Assistance, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Partners West General Brochure, 2011 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Partners' Directory of Resources, 1975-2000 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Partners' Directory of Resources, 1975-2000 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Partners' Directory of Resources, 1975-2000 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Partners' Directory of Resources, 1975-2000 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Partners' Directory of Resources, 1975-2000 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Partners' Family Directory 1991-2000, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Partners' 25th Anniversary Program, 2000 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Partnership, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    folder 1 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    folder 2 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    folder 3 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    folder 4 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    folder 5 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    folder 6 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    folder 7 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    folder 8 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    folder 9 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    folder 10 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    folder 11 of 12
  - Place and Place Index, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    folder 12 of 12
  - Preliminary Report: Partners Indiana Strategic Planning Study, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Presentation by Wolf Von Eckardt, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Presentation of the Founders' Award for Civic Leadership to Lady Bird Johnson, 1985 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Public Art: Resources and Inspiration for Purchasers and Artists, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Script for the Livability Film, 1977 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Selected Grant Booklets, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Selected Grant Booklets, 1981 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities 1988-1990: The First Two Years, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities List of Participants, August 11, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988 - 1992 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988 - 1992 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988 - 1992 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988 - 1992 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities, 1988 - 1992 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to the Board of Directors in Partners for a Livable San Diego, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to the Board of Directors in Partners for a Livable San Diego, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to the Board of Directors in Partners for a Livable San Diego, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Smaller Community Technical Assistance, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Taking up the Call: City Sustainable, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - The Community Assistance Guide, 2011 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - The National Business Council on Livability, 2010 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - The National Business Council on Livability (2012 Edition) (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - The National Center for Community Action, 1995 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - The National Program and Design prepared for the National Council on the Arts, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - The National Program and Design prepared for the National Council on the Arts, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - The Partnership: A Membership Consortium of Partners for Livable Communities 2012-2013 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - The Partnership Notes: Issue 1, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - The Proceedings fo the National Conference on the Urban Enviornment, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Third Decade Reunion & Honors Program: Reconnecting in the New Millennium, 2004 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Towards Livable Communities, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Trustee News, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Trustee News, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Trustee News, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Trustee Obligations: Ways to Contribute, 2012 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Vision, Community, and Spirit, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - We Have Changed Our Name Brochure, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - White Paper: Architectural and Environmental Arts Program, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Series 6: Shared Heritage of the Americas, 1982-1995; (5 boxes)
  Series 6, Shared Heritage of the Americas contains information that looks at the special resources inherent throughout North America, Central America, and the Caribbean.
  - Assessment for World Wildlife Fund of Strategic 1992 Development Opportunities, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Beyond the Horizon: A Concept Paper for the USIA Exhibit at Genoa Expo 1992, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Beyond the Horizon: A Concept Paper for the USIA Exhibit at Genoa Expo 1992, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Campaign - 1992, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Pamphlet - 1992, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Caribbean Heritage: A Voyage of Rediscovery, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Caribbean: Gateway to a New World, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Caribbean: Gateway to a New World, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Caribbean: Gateway to a New World, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Conservation of the Americas: Forum in Commemoration of the Year of the Americas, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Conservation of the Americas: Forum in Commemoration of the Year of the Americas, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Conservation of the Americas: Forum in Commemoration of the Year of the Americas - Transcript, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Conservation of the Americas: Forum in Commemoration of the Year of the Americas - Transcript, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Development of the Atlantic Community 1500 to 1992, 1982 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Final Report Exhibition Planning Grant, National Endowment for the Humanities: The Lost Century, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Final Report to Spain '92, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Journey to Terra Nova: European Enterprise and Native Encounters in the North Atlantic, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Journey to Terra Nova: European Enterprise and Native Encounters in the North Atlantic, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Journey to Terra Nova: European Enterprise and Native Encounters in the North Atlantic, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Place Magazine: "Underwater Archaeology", 1987 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Quincentenary Planning Session, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Report on the Lost Century, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Sea Changes, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Sea Changes, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Sea Changes, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Ship, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 5)